

ANDROID DEVELOPER

Details

Tehran, Iran, Islamic Republic of +989398738141 <u>dalvandsina@yahoo.com</u>

27 MAY 1999

Links

github

linkedin

twitter

instagram

Skills

Java

Kotlin

Android SDK

Dagger2 & Koin (DI)

Retrofit and WebServices

RxJava/RxAndroid

TDD,Unit Testing

Design Patterns

Git / VCS

Google Play Service & Firebase

Languages

Persian

English

Hobbies

Mount climbing, Reading

Profile

Android developer with 3+ years of experience in freelance developing and 1+ year of experience working for a software developing company as senior Android developer and also more than 1+ years experience in PHP and Laravel framework and very interested in learning Flutter (already took the first steps).

And really love new challenges ...

Employment History

Android Developer, 30nama, Tehran

2017 - FEBRUARY 2018

An Android application was developed for Movie and Series website that include a normal movie app feature and additional feature like inside video player(Exo), API encryption and advanced UI/UX (custom view)

Android Developer, Freelance

MARCH 2018 - 2019

make more than 3 android application:

- Fajr Market Online Hypermarket (like Walmart Grocery Deliver concept)
- Fajr Panel Management panel for "Fajr Market" in php-Laravel
- Rose Movie Movie and Series Powerful and beauty app
- Child Lock children monitoring app for Persian user

Android Developer, Samco Company, Tehran

2019 - FEBRUARY 2020

employed as android developer in Samco Software developing company

Android Developer, Citek Company, Remote

APRIL 2020 - PRESENT

Working in company as a Remote Senior Android Developer in international projects.

Education

bachelor of science, Lorestan University, Khorramabad

OCTOBER 2018 - PRESENT

Studying computer engineering

Extra-curricular activities

Android Custom View Tutorial Recoding, arcademy.ir, Tehran

NOVEMBER 2018 - DECEMBER 2018

Record Making advance Custom View tutorial in the Persian language that has more than 80 sells, accessible in below link:

open link

Dagger 2 Tutorial Recording, arcademy.ir, Tehran

AUGUST 2019 - OCTOBER 2019

Record Android Dagger 2 Tutorial advance level in Persian language and Kotlin that have more than 60 sells, accessible in below address:

open link

References

References available upon request